(Raj:)I love this time of the year.
(Raj:)The leaves are turning.
There's a bracing chill in the air.
(Howard:)Plus, there's a whole new crop
of female grad students...
(Howard:)...about to put on just enough winter
weight to make them needy and vulnerable.
(Howard:)That's right, honey, have another calzone.
Daddy can wait.
Isn't there a policy
against dating graduate students?
(Leonard:)No. If you can talk to them,
you can ask them out.
(Raj:)Damn. There's always a catch.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Leslie.
(Leslie:)So, dumb-ass, I heard you made
a grad student throw up last night.
(Sheldon:)The truth can indeed be a finger down
the throat of those unprepared to hear it.
(Sheldon:)But why should I cater
to second-rate minds?
(Leslie:)Because first-rate minds
call you "dumb-ass."
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah? Well...
(Sheldon:)You're a mean person.
Excuse me, Dr. Cooper?
(Girl(arriving):)I'm Ramona Nowitzki.
I was at your talk last night.